Dallas, TX | scott.a.strittmatter@gmail.com | scottstrittmatter.com | GitHub: /mrpancakes | LinkedIn: /scottstrittmatter

Career Objective

I am a full-stack web developer based out of Dallas, TX, with a focus on the MERN stack.

Throughout my eight years of working in digital marketing I became heavily interested in web development. I took self-paced courses and implemented my newly acquired knowledge in my various roles, but knew deep down I wanted to become a full-time developer. At the end of 2020, I enrolled in a full-stack bootcamp and have since developed a number of frontend, backend, and full-stack applications. I believe my marketing background gives me an edge as I have worked with all sides of business to bring projects from inception to deployment across my different roles.

Experience

JPMORGAN CHASE, PLANO, TX

Senior Marketing Automation Specialist, Mar 2019 - Present

- Develop and manage microsite landing templates, email engagement programs, and subsequent reporting through Adobe's marketing automation tool, Marketo.
- Developed five landing page templates to-date that allow for drag-and-drop customization in Marketo, which have been leveraged across many B2C marketing and servicing campaigns.
- Work with various teams across the firm to organize requirements for marketing campaigns being deployed to existing and prospective B2C clients.
- Firm-wide team lead for the five other Marketo instances across JPMorgan Chase.

REALPAGE INC., RICHARDSON, TX

Marketing Automation Specialist, Feb 2017 - Mar 2019

- Managed the promotional, operational, and event-based email & automation campaigns for three business units using Marketo and Salesforce.
- · Created and monitored lead generation for paid advertising campaigns, call trafficking, and form-fills.
- Created and monitored campaigns for event registrations, ensuring proper emails and lead statuses were triggered based on a lead's engagement behavior.
- Managed lead nurturing campaigns to introduce prospects to the Kigo brand in multiple language segmentations.

TANDEM THEORY, ADDISON, TX

CRM Specialist, Nov 2015 - Feb 2017

- Managed the email and SMS programs for At Home using Salesforce Marketing Cloud.
- Deployed emails to over 1 million people each week and provided weekly, monthly, and quarterly performance reports.
- Met weekly with the client to develop a seven-day email marketing calendar with content and placement proposals.

CLUBCORP, DALLAS, TX

Digital CRM Manager, May 2015 - Nov 2015

- Worked exclusively in Eloqua Marketing Automation to create and send email campaigns to roughly 300,000 country and business club members, while also helping club staff troubleshoot issues they experienced with their own email campaigns.
- Created forms and landing pages for various marketing campaigns at both the corporate and club level, and provided reports once campaigns concluded

Digital Marketing Specialist, Jun 2013 - May 2015

- Managed the website content for over 20 country clubs and business clubs using EZ Publish and Members
 First content management systems.
- · Worked daily with club staff to ensure their web content was up-to-date and troubleshot technical issues.
- Assisted each club in managing their email marketing campaigns through Eloqua along with social media training.

 Worked with marketing to create new and fresh campaigns the clubs could use for various membership acquisition programs.

Education

SOUTHERN METHODIST UNIVERSITY

DALLAS, TX

Bootcamp Full-Stack Web Development Candidate (Expected graduation Jul 2021)

UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA

NORMAN, OK

Bachelors of Business Administration Marketing (Dec 2012)

- 2008-2012: Pride of Oklahoma Marching Band Member
- 2010-2012: Founder & President of OU Club Dodgeball Team

Additional Skills

- JavaScript ES6+
- MySql
- MongoDB
- Node
- React
- RESTful APIs
- Third-Party APIs
- Photoshop

Certifications

Marketo Certified Expert